/*All questions in the quiz goes here in the data object.....*/
var data =
[
	[
		{
			"question"	: "What is a productive cough?",
			"option1"	: "One that makes you feel better immediately",
			"option2"	: "One that results in cancer",
			"option3"	: "One that helps expel phlegm from the body",
			"option4"	: "One that causes other symptoms to appear",
			"answer"	: 3
		},
		{
			"question"	: "In stack inserting an element is called _______",
			"option1"	: "pop",
			"option2"	: "push",
			"option3"	: "create",
			"option4"	: "evaluation",
			"answer"	: 2
		},
		{
			"question"	: "In Stack deleting an element is called __________",
			"option1"	: "push",
			"option2"	: "delete",
			"option3"	: "remove",
			"option4"	: "pop",
			"answer"	: 4
		},
		{
			"question"	: "In stack if user tries to remove an element from empty stack . It is ________",
			"option1"	: "Empty collection",
			"option2"	: "Garbage collection",
			"option3"	: "Overflow of stack",
			"option4"	: "Underflow of stack",
			"answer"	: 4
		},
		{
			"question"	: "If user pushes an element in stack which is full then stack becomes ________",
			"option1"	: "underflow",
			"option2"	: "overflow",
			"option3"	: "userflow",
			"option4"	: "crash",
			"answer"	: 2
		},
		{
			"question"	: "In order to keep track of current top most element we need to maintain a variable",
			"option1"	: "True",
			"option2"	: "False",
			"option3"	: "Not Necessarily",
			"option4"	: "User choice",
			"answer"	: 1
		},
		{
			"question"	: "The variable denoting topmost element of stack is ____",
			"option1"	: "first",
			"option2"	: "Top",
			"option3"	: "stack",
			"option4"	: "data",
			"answer"	: 2
		},
		{
			"question"	: "The Top is initialized as _________",
			"option1"	: "-1",
			"option2"	: "1",
			"option3"	: "3",
			"option4"	: "0",
			"answer"	: 1
		},
		{
			"question"	: "Stack is a _________",
			"option1"	: "Linear data structure",
			"option2"	: "Non-Linear Data structure",
			"option3"	: "Multiple Data structure",
			"option4"	: "None",
			"answer"	: 1
		},
		{
			"question"	: "Stack is also called as _______",
			"option1"	: "Non-Restricted DS",
			"option2"	: "Restricted DS",
			"option3"	: "Anti-Restricted",
			"option4"	: "None",
			"answer"	: 2
		},
			]
];